export interface Question {
    question: string;
    answers: string[];
    correctAnswer: string;
  }

export const questions: Question[] = [
    {
        question: "5+3=?",
        answers: ["6", "7", "8", "9"],
        correctAnswer: "8"
    },
    {
        question: "12−5=?",
        answers: ["5", "6", "7", "8"],
        correctAnswer: "7"
    },
    {
        question: "4×2=?",
        answers: ["6", "8", "10", "12"],
        correctAnswer: "8"
    },
    {
        question: "16÷4=?",
        answers: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
        correctAnswer: "4"
    },
    {
        question: "9+6=?",
        answers: ["14", "15", "16", "17"],
        correctAnswer: "15"
    },
    {
        question: "20−9=?",
        answers: ["10", "11", "12", "13"],
        correctAnswer: "11"
    },
    {
        question: "3×5=?",
        answers: ["10", "12", "15", "18"],
        correctAnswer: "15"
    },
    {
        question: "18÷3=?",
        answers: ["5", "6", "7", "8"],
        correctAnswer: "6"
    },
    {
        question: "7+4=?",
        answers: ["10", "11", "12", "13"],
        correctAnswer: "11"
    },
    {
        question: "14−7=?",
        answers: ["5", "6", "7", "8"],
        correctAnswer: "7"
    },
    {
        question: "6×3=?",
        answers: ["15", "16", "17", "18"],
        correctAnswer: "18"
    },
    {
        question: "24÷4=?",
        answers: ["5", "6", "7", "8"],
        correctAnswer: "6"
    },
    {
        question: "8+5=?",
        answers: ["12", "13", "14", "15"],
        correctAnswer: "13"
    },
    {
        question: "15−6=?",
        answers: ["8", "9", "10", "11"],
        correctAnswer: "9"
    },
    {
        question: "2×9=?",
        answers: ["16", "17", "18", "19"],
        correctAnswer: "18"
    },
    {
        question: "21÷7=?",
        answers: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
        correctAnswer: "3"
    },
    {
        question: "10+4=?",
        answers: ["13", "14", "15", "16"],
        correctAnswer: "14"
    },
    {
        question: "17−8=?",
        answers: ["7", "8", "9", "10"],
        correctAnswer: "9"
    },
    {
        question: "3×7=?",
        answers: ["20", "21", "22", "23"],
        correctAnswer: "21"
    },
    {
        question: "30÷5=?",
        answers: ["5", "6", "7", "8"],
        correctAnswer: "6"
    },

  ];
  